elasticpath.com 2019-08-13

# Privacy Policy

## Website Privacy and Cookie Policy

Elastic Path Software Inc. ( **“Elastic Path”** ) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. This Website Privacy and Cookie Policy ( **“Policy”** ) outlines how we handle the collection, use and disclosure of personal information collected from people who visit and otherwise interact with us through [https://www.elasticpath.com](https://www.elasticpath.com/) ( **“website”** ), including how we use cookies and similar technologies. This Policy is intended to assist you in making informed decisions when using our website and is intended to establish responsible and transparent practices for the management of personal information and to satisfy the requirements of rules established by applicable privacy laws and standards in the jurisdictions where we operate.

**By continuing to use our website, you are deemed to consent to the terms of this Policy, including without limitation our use of the cookies described in this Policy.** If you choose to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, or if you subsequently block cookies, you may not be able to access all or part of the content on our website.

This Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by Elastic Path. Other websites that may be accessible through our website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by all third parties prior to providing them with information.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information you Provide

We collect certain personal information directly from you when you visit or use our website. For instance, we may collect the following types of information:

**Inquiries.** We may collect your name, contact information, e-mail address and any information you provide us when you make an inquiry or contact us through our website. We will only use this information to provide you with the information requested or to contact you in order to answer your questions or requests.

**Requests for Elastic Path Products or Services.** We may collect your name, contact information, e-mail address and any other information provided to us when you sign up to receive our newsletter or when you submit a request for more information about Elastic Path products or services. We will only use this information to process and answer your request or to manage our everyday business needs in connection with such request.

**Surveys.** When you visit our website, you may, from time to time, be invited to participate in a survey. In such case and if you decide to participate to our survey, we may collect your location information, email address and other information deemed important to complete such survey.

### What Information We Collect Using Cookies

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit our website, we may collect technical information, using electronic means such as cookies. This information may include information about your visit to our website, including the IP address of your computer and which browser you used to view our website, your operating system, resolution of screen, location, language settings in browsers, the site you came from, keywords searched (if arriving from a search engine), the number of page views, information you entered, advertisements you have seen, etc. This data is used to measure and improve the effectiveness of our website or enhance the experience for our website users. For instance, it may be used to ensure that the products advertised on our website are available in your area or that we are not showing you the same ads repeatedly. We treat this information as personal information when it is associated with your account or contact information. For instance, we may collect and use the following type of information when you visit and/or interact with us on our websites:

**Google Analytics:** We use Google Analytics which allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to, page views, source and time spent on our website. This information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning that it cannot be tracked back to individuals.

**Google AdWords:** We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise Elastic Path across the Internet and to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our websites. AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of the website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site or this could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device. The cookie is only used to indicate to other websites that you have visited a particular page on our website, so that they may show you ads relating to that page. If you do not wish to participate in our Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out directly with Google.

**Interest-based Advertising.** Elastic Path may also allow a limited number of cookies from trusted third parties to be installed on your hard drive directly from our website. Our website may include third-party advertising and links to other websites which may be used to generate personalized advertisements. Personalized ads, sometimes referred to as interest-based or behavioral ads, are ads based upon information about you, such as your page views on our website, your information requests or purchases on our websites. We do not provide any personal information to advertisers or to third party sites that display interest-based ads on our websites. However, advertisers and other third-parties (including the ad networks, ad-serving companies, and other service providers they may use) may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized ad or content displayed on our websites are part of the group that the ad or content is directed towards. Advertisers or ad companies working on their behalf sometimes use technology to serve the ads that appear on our websites directly to your browser. They may also use cookies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize ad content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that advertisers and third party sites may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third party websites are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.

### Sharing Your Information

Elastic Path will use the information you provide only for the purposes identified in this Policy. Elastic Path will only disclose information about you to its affiliated companies, business partners and authorized agents who assist us in performing our functions.

We will not sell or otherwise disclose information collected from you to other third parties, except in those limited cases where we are legally required to do so.

### Safeguards

Elastic Path has taken commercially reasonable steps to assure the security of any sensitive information that is transmitted to and from our website. We will cease all communication and use of your information upon your request. Your privileges for access to certain resources on this website may then be affected.

### Change of Website Privacy and Cookie Policy

Elastic Path will review and update its policies and procedures as required to keep current with rules and regulations, new technologies, standards and customer concerns. Our Policy and related privacy practices may therefore change from time to time. We will post any changes on our website and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

This Policy was last updated on June 29, 2018.

### Contact Us

Should further information be needed regarding this Policy, please [contact us.](https://www.elasticpath.com/company/contact-us)
